<Database>
    <GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_EN_ADDON_MOREEVENTS">
    
        <LanguageCode>en</LanguageCode>
        <LanguageNameLocalized>English</LanguageNameLocalized>
        
        <Contributors>
            <Name>James B</Name>
        </Contributors>
        
        <LocalizedStrings>

            <!-- Event names -->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>EVENT_CRASH</LocID>                     
			<Text>Accident</Text>  
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>EVENT_PANDEMIC</LocID>                  
			<Text>Disease Outbreak</Text>  
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>EVENT_NATURAL_DISASTER</LocID>          
			<Text>Disaster</Text>  
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<!-- ########### EVENTS ########### -->
			<!-- Disaster -->

            <GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_JM_EVENT_EXPLOSION_DESC</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>An explosion has occured in a mall nearby, due to a fatal gas leak from one of it's restaurants and a lighter. Police are investigating on what caused the gas leak. All nearby hospitals should prepare for a moderate amount of injuries. </Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_JM_EVENT_NUCLEAR_MELTDOWN_DESC</LocID>         	              
			<Text>BREAKING NEWS! A nuclear meltdown has been recorded in a nearby city, and many injuries has affected the cities population. Rescue services are on the scene trying to evacuate the city. An epidemic is possible due to damaged healthcare facilities there.</Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_JM_EVENT_VOLCANIC_ERUPTION_DESC</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>BREAKING NEWS! A volcano in nearby to a major city has erupted and caused major damages to infrastructure and has killed and injured many citizens. People are being evacuated by authorities and hospitals should prepare for a large amount of injuries. </Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_JM_EVENT_LANDSLIDE_DESC</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>BREAKING NEWS! A landslide has occured in a nearby city on the side of a famous mountain. Many residential and commercial areas are damaged and the residents are severly injured or dead. Hospitals in nearby cities should prepare for a potential epidemic and trauma patients.</Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_JM_EVENT_DAM_BURST_DESC</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>BREAKING NEWS! A Dam has burst in a nearby state/province and many cities are affected by flooding. The governer has issued a state of emergency and 5 million citizens are being evacuated. Injured people are being brought by helicopter to neighbouring states/provinces. Hospitals nearby should prepare for a large amount of trauma patients. </Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_JM_EVENT_FIRE1_DESC</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>A fire has occured at a office building due to a faulty powerbox. Firefighters are evacuating many in the building. Nearby hospitals should prepare for a big amount of burn patients. </Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_JM_EVENT_FIRE2_DESC</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>BREAKING NEWS! A major fire has erupted in a International Airport. Firefighters and Police are evacuating passengers and staff. The fire seems to have been caused by a terrorist lighting up several matches and putting them next to a fuel tank. Police are still investigating how did he gain access to the fuel tanks.</Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_JM_EVENT_FIRE3_DESC</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>A fire has broke out in a Shopping Mall by the city centre. Many are being evacuated and some are injured. Your hospital should prepare for injured and burned patients.</Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_JM_EVENT_HURRICANE1_DESC</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>BREAKING NEWS! A category 3 hurricane has rocked the east side of the country. Many are displaced from their homes and many are injured. Hospitals should prepare for a giant amount of traumas.</Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_JM_EVENT_TORNADO1_DESC</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>BREAKING NEWS! A EF 3 tornado has torn down a neighbouring suburb. Many buildings are destroyed and many are injured. Ambulances and rescue services are on the scene rescuing survivors. Hospitals should prepare for trauma and sick patients. </Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<!-- Accident -->
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_JM_EVENT_AEROPLANE_CRASH_DESC</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>BREAKING NEWS! A Turkish Airliner has crashed in a major town due to a engine failure caused by damage from a previous flight. Buildings near the crash has collapsed and many are injured. Hospitals in the cities are being overwhelmed, so some patients are being transported to neighbouring cities. </Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_JM_EVENT_REMOTE_PLANE_CRASH_DESC</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>A private plane has crashed in a nearby forest, and the cause is unknown. Few are injured or dead and your hospitals nearby should keep a little space for some trauma patients. </Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_JM_EVENT_LORRY_ACCIDENT_DESC</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>BREAKING NEWS! A lorry has crashed into a several cars and two small shop. Tens of people were injured and the lorry driver was arrested on sight. Your Hospital should prepare trauma equipment for trauma patients.</Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_JM_EVENT_SINKING_SHIP_DESC</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>BREAKING NEWS! A cruise ship has crashed into a island off a city due to a broken steering wheel. Rescue services are currently evacuating whoever is on board. Hospitals nearby should prepare for many trauma patients</Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_JM_EVENT_EXPLODED_SHIP_DESC</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>BREAKING NEWS! A oil tanker has exploded of the coast of the city due to a fire on board. Burning oil has also leaked into the sea, causing ecosystem disruption and closing of beaches nearby. Rescue services are currently evacuating whoever is on board. Hospitals nearby should prepare for several trauma patients.</Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_JM_EVENT_BUILDCOLLAPSE1_DESC</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>A shopping centre has collapsed for unknown reasons. Firefighters are finding survivors within the debri. Many survivors are injured and are being transported to nearby hospitals.</Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_JM_EVENT_BUS_ACCIDENT_DESC</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>A college bus has just crashed into a barber shop due to the bus driver suffering from Narcolepsy. Many are injured and are being transported to hospitals.</Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_JM_EVENT_CHAIN_COLLISION_DESC</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>BREAKING NEWS! The fog has caused a chain collision at a highway entering the city. Some are injured and are being transported to hospitals, as the firefighters put out fires.</Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_JM_EVENT_TRAIN_DERAILMENT_DESC</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>BREAKING NEWS! A train passing by has derailed and crashed off the bridge. Rescue services are on the scene finding survivors. The Train Driver has been found dead and many are injured.</Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_JM_EVENT_CHEMICAL_LEAK_DESC</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>BREAKING NEWS! A chemical factory has leaked dangerous chemicals like Sodium Hydroxide and Ammonia. Residents nearby are advised to stay indoors and close doors and windows. Burned and sick patients are being transported into the city.</Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<!-- Disease Outbreak -->
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_JM_EVENT_FOOD_POISONING1_DESC</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>A very famous crisps/chips brand has been contaminated with Clostridium Botulinum and has been removed from many shelves after cases of Botulism has been linked to this crisp/chip brand. Hospitals should prepare for cases of Botulism.</Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_JM_EVENT_FOOD_POISONING2_DESC</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>A chicken processing plant has been contaminated with Salmonella Typhi which is the bacteria which causes Salmonella. The CDC recommend citizens to cook their chicken thoroughly at 73.8*C / 165*F to kill off the Salmonella Typhi bacteria. Hospitals should expect many cases of Salmonella.</Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_JM_EVENT_FOOD_POISONING3_DESC</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>A pig farm has been infected with multiple pathogens from a infected pig that accidentally ate manure when it fell into its food and then it infected others. Hospitals should expect more food poisoning cases.</Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_JM_EVENT_FOOD_POISONING4_DESC</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>BREAKING NEWS! A processing plant has drained their sewage into a major reservoir and has caused water contamination in many cities and states/provinces. The owner of the processing plant has been arrested and fined along with their executives. Hospitals should expect more diseases and poisonings.</Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_JM_EVENT_EPIDEMIC1_DESC</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>BREAKING NEWS! Several chipanzees infected with several deadly diseases has infected several people including a member of the Ministry of Enviroment, the CDC has implemented a major lockdown in a major city as there is many cases of several deadly diseases. A epidemic is likely to erupt in many other cities.</Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_JM_EVENT_EPIDEMIC2_DESC</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>BREAKING NEWS! Many of Bubonic Plague cases has been reported in a nearby state due to a rat infestation at a factory. The Centre For Disease Control or also known as the CDC, has implemented Lockdowns in the state and has issued a public health emergency. Hospitals should prepare for many patients with the Plague.</Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_JM_EVENT_EPIDEMIC3_DESC</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>BREAKING NEWS! Several cases of the Nipah Virus Infection has been recorded in a 5 star hotel nearby. Many has been quarantined and the CDC has issued a public health emergency. Please present to the nearest hospital if you are experiencing symptoms of the Nipah Virus Infection.</Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_JM_EVENT_SEASON1_DESC</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>Allergy Season has come! Hospitals should expect for more allergy related illnesses.</Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_JM_EVENT_SEASON2_DESC</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>Allergy Season has been worse than usual, hospitals should expect more severe allergy relasted illnesses.</Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_JM_EVENT_BIOTERRORIST1_DESC</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>BREAKING NEWS! A bioterrorist attack has just occured in the city center, many are ill with Anthrax. The CDC has immediately quarantined many individuals. Hospitals should prepare for an outbreak of Anthrax.</Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<!-- ########### News ########### -->
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_WORLD_EVENT_CIVIL_WAR_CRISIS</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>A civil war has started nation-wide, causing a {1}% increases in trauma patients. </Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_WORLD_EVENT_CIVIL_WAR_CRISIS_TEXT</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>A rebellion calling themselves the Liberal Liberation Army has started a civil war to end the nation's 'tyrannical regime', and the war causes {1}% more trauma patients to come. </Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_WORLD_EVENT_WAR</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>The nation you are in has gone to war with another country, causing a {1}% increases in trauma patients. </Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_WORLD_EVENT_WAR_TEXT</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>The nation you are in has gone to war with another country because of disputed land, causing {1}% more trauma patients to come. </Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_WORLD_EVENT_PROTESTS</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>A protest has started in a nearby city, causing {1}% increases in trauma patients. </Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_WORLD_EVENT_PROTESTS_TEXT</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>A protest has erupted in a nearby city due to police brutality, and this causes a {1}% increase in trauma patients. </Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_WORLD_EVENT_EPIDEMIC</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>A epidemic has erupted in the capital of the nation, causing {1}% increase in infections.</Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_WORLD_EVENT_EPIDEMIC_TEXT</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>A epidemic has erupted in the capital of the nation due to equipment shortages from the COVID-19 pandemic. A wide-spread epidemic is possible. Hospitals should prepare for a lot of infections. </Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_WORLD_EVENT_BUDGET_CUT</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>A cut to the healthcare budget causes {1}% lower insurance payments. </Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_WORLD_EVENT_BUDGET_CUT_TEXT</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>The Prime Minister/President/Dictator has cut the healthcare budget causing a {1}% decrease in insurance payments. </Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_WORLD_EVENT_BUDGET_INCREASE</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>A increase to the healthcare budget causes {1}% higher insurance payments. </Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_WORLD_EVENT_BUDGET_INCREASE_TEXT</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>The Prime Minister/President has increased the healthcare budget causing a {1}% increase in insurance payments. </Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_WORLD_EVENT_KAREN_STRIKES</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>A terrible health inspector has wrote a bad review about your hospital causing {1}% less patients to come. </Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_WORLD_EVENT_KAREN_STRIKES_TEXT</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>A terrible health inspector has wrote a bad review about your hospital. The Ministry of Health has acknowledged the review and has discouraged people from going to your hospital causing {1}% less patients to come. </Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_WORLD_EVENT_TERRORISM</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>A terrorist organisation has terrorised the state causing {1}% increase in trauma patients. </Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_WORLD_EVENT_TERRORISM_TEXT</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>A terrorist organisation has terrorised the state causing {1}% increase in trauma patients. </Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_WORLD_EVENT_MURDERER</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>A murderer has been found on the lose and is hurting many innocents causing {1}% increase in trauma patients. </Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>MOD_WORLD_EVENT_MURDERER_TEXT</LocID>         		                    
			<Text>A murderer has been found on the lose and is hurting many innocents causing {1}% increase in trauma patients. </Text>
			</GameDBLocalizedString>

        </LocalizedStrings>
    </GameDBStringTable>
</Database>
    